NANDAN KUMAR HG

+39 3472809168 | Via Curzola 10, Padova, Italy 35135

nandanhg2222@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/nandan-kumar-hg-42884b184

SUMMARY

Analyst with over 2 years of full time work experience in analyzing, designing data and creating aircraft technical documentation. A team player and a highly motivated individual willing to learn new technologies. Able to adapt to different work culture and always ready to accept new challenges.

SKILLS

- Qlik sense
- Tableau
- Power BI
- SAP MM
- AutoCAD
- Catiav5
- JIRA
- HTML
- CSS • Figma
- JavaScript
- ISO draw
- UI/UX design
- Web design
- Arbotextepic editor
- Adobe premiere pro
- Adobe Illustrator
- Project management
- Digital marketing
- Technical writing
- Technical service

EDUCATION

Masters in Engineering Management

Oct 2021 - Jun 2023

Universita degli studi di Padova, Italy

Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering

Aug 2015 – Jul 2019

Vishvesvarayya Technological University, East Point collage of Engineering, Bengaluru, India CGPA: 8.22 out of 10

WORK EXPERIENCE

BRAINNEST Business Consulting and Services, Bremen, Germany Project Management Trainee

May 2022 – Jun 2022

Part of the project management team, responsible for planning, execution, monitoring, controlling and closing out projects. My responsibilities include:

- Coordination and supervision of project from the kick-off to close-out.
- Analyzing stakeholder's expectations.
- Prioritizing and planning the product backlog and sprint backlogs.

- Analyzing and assorting project risks by maintaining risk register regarding minimizing risk.
- Establishing and maintaining a constant stream of communication between different departments of the project for efficient functioning.
- Used agile methodologies, with specific reference to the scrum framework in JIRA.

CAPGEMINI CONSULTING INDIA PVT LTD, BANGALORE, INDIA Analyst

Aug 2019 - Sep 2021

Part of the team responsible for developing and maintaining aircraft technical documentations and project dashboard creations. My responsibilities included:

- Writing aircraft maintenance procedures and descriptions in various ATA chapters for AMM, AIPC, CMM, SRM, ITEM and TLMC manuals (Technical documentation).
- Providing technical service for Aircraft Maintenance Technicians.
- Data visualization, creating dashboards using tableau.

CERTIFICATIONS

Qlik Sense Business Analyst Qualification.

LANGUAGES

- English
- Italian (Beginner)

HOBBIES

- Portrait pencil sketching
- Photography

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in this application to be processed for the purposes of current and future recruitment processes.